

SKILLS

- Goal development planning
- . Staff appraisals
- Training and development
- Task delegation

ELIANIS MEDINA

- BOGOTA D.C. COLOMBIA 111031
- +573008828214
- elianismedina05@outlook.com

SUMMARY

Strategic leader with extensive team management experience. Builds training, mentoring and development opportunities to drive performance. Shares robust resource planning and project delivery expertise. Open and inclusive collaborator with strong team building skills. Excels at root cause analysis and dispute resolution. Leads by example to create positive and supportive working environments.

EXPERIENCE

April 2023 - September 2023

Team leader iQor Colombia | Envigado, Antioquia

- Overseeing and assessing customer service staff activities, and providing them with regular performance-related feedback.
- Strategizing and monitoring the daily activities of customer service operations.
- . Assisting customer service staff with duties where required.
- Training staff in areas of customer service and company policies.
- Managing cashier coverage and customer flow to ensure proficient customer service.
- . Monitoring and authenticating returns, exchanges, and voids.
- . Investigating and solving customer service complaints.
- Assisting with the development and implementation of service policies, and explaining these to staff and customers.
- Maintaining documentation pertaining to customer service department activities.
- Performing additional duties where needed.

July 2021 - January 2023

Team Leader Asurion Colombia | Bogota D.C, Bogota D.C

- Overseeing and assessing customer service staff activities, and providing them with regular performance-related feedback.
- Strategizing and monitoring the daily activities of customer service operations.
- Assisting customer service staff with duties where required.
- Training staff in areas of customer service and company policies.
- Managing cashier coverage and customer flow to ensure proficient customer service.
- . Monitoring and authenticating returns, exchanges, and voids.
- Investigating and solving customer service complaints.
- Assisting with the development and implementation of service policies, and explaining these to staff and customers.

- Maintaining documentation pertaining to customer service department activities.
- Performing additional duties where needed.

October 2020 - May 2021

Customer Service Supervisor Teleperformace | Barranquilla, Atlántico

- Overseeing and assessing customer service staff activities, and providing them with regular performance-related feedback.
- Strategizing and monitoring the daily activities of customer service operations.
- Assisting customer service staff with duties where required.
- Training staff in areas of customer service and company policies.
- Managing agents coverage and customer flow to ensure proficient customer service.
- Monitoring and authenticating returns, exchanges, and voids.
- Investigating and solving customer service complaints.
- Assisting with the development and implementation of service policies, and explaining these to staff and customers.
- Maintaining documentation pertaining to customer service department activities.
- Performing additional duties where needed.

May 2016 - October 2020

Technical Support Consultant Sutrherland Global Services | Barranquilla, Atlántico

- . Identifying hardware and software solutions.
- · Troubleshooting technical issues.
- Diagnosing and repairing faults.
- . Resolving network issues.
- . Installing and configuring hardware and software.
- Speaking to customers to quickly get to the root of their problem.
- Providing timely and accurate customer feedback.
- Talking customers through a series of actions to resolve a problem.
- Following up with clients to ensure the problem is resolved.
- Replacing or repairing the necessary parts.
- Supporting the roll-out of new applications.
- Providing support in the form of procedural documentation.
- . Managing multiple cases at one time.

EDUCATION

2010

Certificate of Higher Education | FINANCE FUNDACION UNIVERSITARIA SAN MARTIN SEC

FUNDACION UNIVERSITARIA SAN MARTIN SEDE CARIBE, Puerto Colombia, ATL

. [Degree] Graduate

LANGUAGES

Spanish: First Language

English: C

Advanced